{
    "subject": "resource/Charlie_Chan_Carries_On_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Sol_M._Wurtzel",
    "human_readable": "Sol M. Wurtzel produced the film Charlie Chan Carries On.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8708332777023315,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8648190498352051,
            "question": "What is the title of the film produced by Sol M. Wurtzel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7636918425559998,
            "question": "What was the storyline of 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7320157885551453,
            "question": "What genre was the film 'Charlie Chan Carries On' likely in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6874294877052307,
            "question": "When was 'Charlie Chan Carries On' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6313104033470154,
            "question": "Who were some actors who might have been in 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6283349990844727,
            "question": "What role did Charlie Chan play in the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5906939506530762,
            "question": "How successful was 'Charlie Chan Carries On' upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5786095857620239,
            "question": "Was Sol M. Wurtzel involved in any other aspects of filmmaking besides directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549226403236389,
            "question": "Are there any other films associated with Sol M. Wurtzel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sol M. Wurtzel produced the film Charlie Chan Carries On.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3534_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Sol M. Wurtzel involved in any other aspects of filmmaking besides directing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3534_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How successful was 'Charlie Chan Carries On' upon its release?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3534_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Charlie Chan play in the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3534_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3534_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that \"1931's Charlie Chan Carries On, produced by Sol M. Wurtzel,\" providing evidence to support the statement that Sol M. Wurtzel produced the film \"Charlie Chan Carries On.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}